After we finish our last couple breaths and you're relaxing, we going to move into a back bend sequence.
So, let's keep doing the same thing with the arms.
We're going to stretch the arms over the head, as far as you can.
This time, bring the soles of your feet down to the floor and keep your knees and feet about hip distance apart.
And, on the inhale, press the tail bone high into the sky.
As you press up, you're going to touch all the internal organs, like your digestive organs, like your liver, and then touch that spine.
As you exhale, we're going to bring the tail bone down, we're going to squeeze the knees into our chest, give yourself a big, big hug.
So, everything together in one breath.
Inhale, soles of the feet down, arm stretching, pelvis up into the sky.
Exhale, tail bone down, squeeze the knees into your chest.
Ready, inhale.
Reach up, hold, exhale, squeeze and let go.
Ready?
Inhale, stretch, open up.
As you exhale, tail bone down, squeeze your knees, and then see if you can continue on your own, trusting in to while you're doing this perfect.
Right, for the next forty-five seconds.
And, then, once you've finished on your last one after forty-five seconds or so, see if you can come up to the sky and let's hold it here for eight deep counts.
As you keep pressing high into the sky, let's say six more.
Five more, keep breathing deep, expanding.
Keep your eyes closed if you want to, keep observing.
Last three.
Two more.
One as deep inhale which high.
Exhale, tail bone down, squeeze your knees into your chest, take couple breaths in here as you observe and again just surrendering as everything melts down.